When you look at it like this, it kind of looks like Oksan and the girl.
こうやって見ると、なんかオクサンと少女みたいだね
I feel like a girl, but
少女感出てるけど、
Something...
なんか...
Oksan doesn't suit me at all.
オクサンってなんかちょっと似合わないね
Doesn't it suit you?
似合わない?
It really doesn't suit me.
めっちゃ似合わない
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I've been asked some questions.
なんか問い合わさってきたね
cold?
寒い?
Still not used to it?
まだ慣れてない?
This is it.
これちょい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Let's try it again.
もう一回しようね
Let's try again.
もう一回しよう
もう 一回しよう
How many times did you say that earlier?
さっき何回言ったの?
How many times did I say that?
何回言ったの?
sex.
セックス
About twice.
2回くらい
Does it feel better inside?
中の方が気持ちいいの?
Take it and save it.
食い取りしといて
yes.
そう
Have you never eaten anything?
食い取りしていたことないの?
A very beautiful pussy.
めっちゃ綺麗なおまんこ
Let's watch the video together again.
また一緒に見ようかな、動画
The one showing the pussy.
おまんこ映してるやつ
This is so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗だね、これ
Does it change with your pussy?
おまんこと変わる?
What is it?
何でしょ?
You like this sound, right?
この音好きでしょ?
I guess you like this.
好きなんでしょう、これ
Oh no, I'm getting loud.
やばい、声出ちゃう
feeling
気持ち
good?
いい?
Do you feel good?
気 持 ちいい?
I'm excited.
くりくりしてる
what happened?
どうしたの?
I've never been here before, like this.
ここで行ったことないの、こうやって
Isn't there?
ないの?
But it's kind of weird, but it's fine.
でもなんかくりくりしてるけど、結構
What do you think?
どうなの?
Yeah?
うん?
What's going on?
何が起こってんの?
Don't you feel it?
感じてんじゃないの?
I just don't understand it.
ちょっと分かんないから、ってのを
Is it really strong?
すげえ強い?
I'm doing it weakly.
弱くやってる
Does this feel good?
これ気持ちいい?
It feels good, it looks good.
気持ちいい、良さそうだよね
tickles.
くすぐったい
Are you ticklish?
くすぐったいの?
From above your face?
顔の上から?
Yeah.
うん
Is this good?
これはいい?
I feel it.
感じてる
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I want to make use of this, but I don't need it.
これで生かしたいんだけど、いらない
This feels good, right?
これ気持ちいいでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Doesn't it feel good?
気持ちいいんじゃないの?
I'll definitely go with this.
行くよね、これ、きっと
Tell me.
教えてよ
Don't you need it?
いらないの?
Liar.
嘘つき
is
だ
Does it feel good?
って 気持ちいい良さそうなの?
Yeah.
うん
I hate it more than I hate it.
嫌がってるよりも嫌だよ
Do you like Kurilla too?
クリラも好き?
Yeah.
うん
I'm sleeping a lot.
めっちゃ寝てるよ
I'm already sleeping really well here.
ここもうすっげえ寝てる
Bring out the rice.
おしいつき出して
what?
何?
It felt good, right?
気持ちよかったでしょ?
I felt it just now.
さっきすぎ感じたじゃん
I'll lick it all over here.
舐めてあげるよ、ここいっぱい
I'll lick it for you.
舐めてあげるからね
Do you like delicious food?
おしい好きなの?
good
好
It's okay.
き だよ
what?
何?
Smoldering?
くすぶったい?
Is it smoldering?
くすぶったいの?
Really?
本当に?
interesting?
面白い?
Who is Chinko?
ちんこさんって?
Is it okay to include this?
これ入れていいんだよね?
hey
ね
Yeah
え ね
picture.
え
Did you stretch it with your fingers?
指 で伸ばした?
Yeah.
うん
Raise your hands high.
手を高くして
Didn't you know you could feel the muscles of a man?
男の人、筋体も感じるの知らなかった?
Is everything good so far?
ここまではいい?
to this point?
ここまで?
It hurts.
痛いな
Toward my back?
うちの後ろに向けて?
I like you, don't you?
僕好きだよね
cormorant
う
Toward the back of Chi?
ち の後ろに向けて?
String.
ひもじ